Lucas Portet

lucasportet@gmail.com +336-789-945-75 lucasportet.com

Summary

I'm Lucas, a full-stack developer focused on making meaningful interfaces and experiences. Working at the crossroad of technology, design and business, I like to see my role as the bridge between the chaos of the machine and human language.

Education

Epitech

MS Computer science (2017 - 2022)
Concentration in web applications, interactions and low-level technologies.

EF San Francisco

Intensive english course (summer 2016)

Experience

SII - Full stack developer (July 2018 to Dec 2018)

Built a visual dashboard for scrum teams. Agile project management. Used Vue, Node, Express and Mongo.

Gang of pizza - Community manager (2016 to 2018)

Managed the digital presence of the company. Targeted ad campaigns. Creation of social media graphics.

PAC Pizza Chef School - Assistant trainer (2016 & 2018 summers) Pizza ATM training course in Cincinnati (2016) and Toronto (2018).

Skills

Languages	Frameworks	Tools	Design
Javascript	Vue	Git	Adobe Suite
Python	React	Scrum	Sketch
C++	Node	Mongo	UX research
Swift	Express	Webpack	Design thinking

Languages

French	English	Spanish
Native	Professional	Notions

Misc

Born	Live in	Driving license	Personality
15/06/1999	Rennes, FR	Yes	ENTP-A